quadcashprofitsystem.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy — keithdougherty.com

This privacy policy describes how Xtreme Marketing Services, Inc (Keith Dougherty) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website keithdougherty.com / xmsusa.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as name and billing address

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * If Xtreme Markting is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personal information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here.

**Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of  Xtreme Markting. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Analytics Data Gathering**

We use third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics to measure traffic and website usage. One feature we use in Google Analytics is non-personally identifiable 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests), which we use to improve our service.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Deletion / Deactivation**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We also encrypt customer information in our database so that customers name and address is never stored in plain text. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please contact us, if you have any questions about security on our Web site.

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and is processed by Authorize.net. If you choose to use a third party payment option, such as PayPal, to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.

**Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.  
Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@xmsua.com.

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.  
Contact Information:

Xtreme Marketing Services, Inc.  
1391 NW St Lucie West Blvd  
Suite 247  
Port St Lucie, FL 34986  
772-924-1717
